UI Designer Software Engineer Electronic Engineer

# LOOUIS LOW



#### **ABOUT ME**

Il have worked in an embedded system domain for ten years. I am primarily prototyping Electronic applications for Automation,
Monitoring and Signal Processing. I also make UI Designs and Frontend-Dev for Embedded
Applications, Web Apps, Websites, TV Apps, Mobile Apps, and as well as Graphic Designs to create materials for marketing and user interface.

## **CONTACT ME**

**PHONE NO** (+6) 016 4910 454

**EMAIL** 

loouis@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://loouislow81.github.io

SOCIAL

dev.to/loouislow twitter.com/loouislow github.com/loouislow81



#### **EXPERIENCE**

dogsbarkSoftware Engineer (architect)Canada2004-2020Embedded Design, Firmware Design, Prototyping and Auto-

mation. Machine Learning and Sound Effect middleware en-

gineering.

Goody Software Engineer (frontend) Malaysia 2016-2017, Craft UI Material Design & UI Design System. Pure CSS FX

without JS. Create custom frontend devtools and boiler-

plates with added CLI automation.

Internet Mastermind

2014-2015

2018-2019

Software Engineer (frontend)

Malavsia

Implement UI and UX for marketing applications with Bootstrap UI framework. Frontend and Backend UI prototyping.

Custom landing page web design for marketer.

## **EDUCATIONS**

Shrewsbury College Visual Art & Design

UN

2008-2009

I also am artist. I gave myself a chance to step into a little bit deeper into the art. Also, I am a perfectionist either in UI or

UX.

Univ. Manchester

**Electrical & Electronic Engineering** 

UK

2002-2005 I was always wanting to be an inventor like robotic, anything since I was a little kid. But, well, they all came true. I just kept

doing it. Never stop.

Chung Ling H. S.

1995-2000

Form 5

Malaysia

Just an ordinary student not very fond of school subjects, beside the computer programming and science classes.

Never a good chance in Art class.

# SKILLS

Embedded Development	Software Development	_
Linux, Prototyping	Essential for Eng.	
Electronic Development	Project Management	
Firmware Design	Kanban, Automate	
Web Development	Design	
Frontend, Modular	UI Design, Component Design, Material Design	